// array of questions
var quizQuestions = [
    {
        question: "commonly used data types do NOT include",
        choices: ['strings', 'booleons', 'alerts', 'numbers'],
        answer:  'alerts'
    },
    {
        question: "what is the default behavior called that is used to move declarations to the top of the current scope?",
        choices: ['hoisting', 'arranging', 'sorting', 'jumping'],
        answer: 'hoisting'
    },
    {
        question: "in javascript, what is used in conjunction with HTML to 'react' to certain elements",
        choices: ['events', 'regex', 'condition', 'booleon'],
        answer: 'events'
    },
    {
        question: "in javascript, what element is used to store and manipulate text, usually in multiples?",
        choices: ['recorders', 'arrays', 'variables', 'strings'],
        answer: 'strings'
    },
    {
        question: "what is considered the most popular programming language in the world?",
        choices: ['swift', 'HTML', 'javascript', 'ruby'],
        answer: 'javascript'
    },
    {
        question: "what is the name of the statement that is used to exit or end a loop?",
        choices: ['falter statement','break statement','conditional statement','close statement',],
        answer: 'break statement'
    },
    {
        question: "commonly used data types do NOT include",
        choices: ['strings','booleons','alerts','numbers'],
        answer: 'alerts'
    },
    {
        question: "any field declared with the keyword _____ is constant",
        choices: ['constant', 'static', 'final', 'const'],
        answer: 'const'
    },
    {
        question: "the condition of an IF/ELSE statement is enclosed in",
        choices: ['curly braces', 'sing quotes', 'parenthesis', 'double quotes'],
        answer: 'parenthesis'
    },

    {
        question: "arrays in javascript can be used to store ",
        choices: ['booleons', 'numbers and strings', 'other arrays', 'all of the above'],
        answer: 'all of the above'
    }
]